{
    "subject": "resource/Dr._Who_and_the_Daleks",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Dr. Who and the Daleks",
    "human_readable": "The label of Dr. Who and the Daleks is 'Dr. Who and the Daleks'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9798944592475891,
            "question": "What is the label of Dr. Who and the Daleks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9166586995124817,
            "question": "Is there a real-world connection to the label 'Dr. Who and the Daleks'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8599214553833008,
            "question": "Is 'Dr. Who and the Daleks' a fictional entity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8420906662940979,
            "question": "Who are the main characters in 'Dr. Who and the Daleks'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8116381168365479,
            "question": "What genre does 'Dr. Who and the Daleks' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7702160477638245,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in 'Dr. Who and the Daleks'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.729300856590271,
            "question": "Are there any spin-offs or related works based on 'Dr. Who and the Daleks'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6819822788238525,
            "question": "What makes 'Dr. Who and the Daleks' so enduringly popular?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6559879779815674,
            "question": "How has the popularity of 'Dr. Who and the Daleks' evolved over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6492322683334351,
            "question": "What impact has 'Dr. Who and the Daleks' had on popular culture?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Dr. Who and the Daleks is 'Dr. Who and the Daleks'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8262_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has the popularity of 'Dr. Who and the Daleks' evolved over time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8262_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes 'Dr. Who and the Daleks' so enduringly popular?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8262_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any spin-offs or related works based on 'Dr. Who and the Daleks'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8262_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8262_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8262_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8262_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8262_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8262_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8262_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8262_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8262_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8262_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8262_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text explicitly states: \"Dr.  Who and the Daleks \u2013 The Official Story of the Films\". This confirms that the label of the book is indeed \"Dr. Who and the Daleks\". \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "To evaluate whether the information in the documents supports the triple, I will look for any mention of \"author\", \"office\", or \"award\" related to the main subject, which is \"Dr. Who and the Daleks\".\n\nThe only relevant piece of information is the document with file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8262/re-ranker-msmarco/70.txt, where it is mentioned that:\n\n\"... On balance, Dr Who And The Daleks is a flawed but very watchable attempt at adapting an important TV story from early \u2018Doctor Who\u2019 instalments for the silver screen...\"\n\nHowever, there is no mention of any author, office, or award related to \"Dr. Who and the Daleks\".\n\nTherefore, I can say that the triple \"The label of Dr. Who and the Daleks is 'Dr. Who and the Daleks'.\" is supported by the documents.\n\nSo, my answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about \"Dr. Who and the Daleks,\" including its release year (1965), cast members, and screenplay details, which supports that the label of Dr. Who and the Daleks is indeed \"Dr. Who and the Daleks.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}